<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>More Consumables and Mutagens (Continued)</name>
  	<packageId>Mlie.MoreConsumablesAndMutagens</packageId>
	<author>AtomicRavioli</author>
	<url>https://github.com/emipa606/MoreConsumablesAndMutagens</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies />
	<loadAfter />
	<description>Update of AtomicRaviolis mod for RimWorld 1.1
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=939909531

[img]https://raw.githubusercontent.com/emipa606/RimWorld-Wrapper/master/Notice.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/MoreConsumablesAndMutagens
	
For a complete list of content:
https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=33284.0

--- Original Description ---
Adds a collection of various consumable items with varying effects.

Oracalium:
Neolithic blend of powdered herbs that is traditionally used by Oracles in tribal societies. Users never build tolerance to it. Addictive. Repeated usage develop semi permanent effects.

Craftable and purchasable.


Ambrosia Iced Tea:
Drink made from ambrosia that calms the drinker down, and without addictive chance. Not as potent as Ambrosia but slightly different effects.

Craftable and purchasable.


Hearth Brew:
Warming beverage for winter time, slightly alcoholic and makes the drinker more festive. Made from slightly fermented berries.

Craftable and purchasable.


Herbal Tincture:
Blend of various herbal medicines that help the user build an immunity to a disease, while making the user drowsy. Effects last 1 day.

Craftable and purchasable.


Ichorio:
Rare iridescent fluid that permanently alters the brain chemistry of the drinker, giving them permanent buffs at the cost of pain sensitivity.

Purchasable.

Taking a mutagen pill puts the user in a mutagenic reaction state. It begins with an initial phase before the effects kick in. After some time, the mutagen starts working. When active, the mutagen randomly gives the user mutations. Mutations are chosen randomly from a pool, some mutations cancel out others. Mutagen pills are highly refined, often giving more beneficial mutations than harmful ones. There is, however, a small chance that the user might not mutate at all. All mutagen pills are purchasable only.

Sil:
Mutagen that is popular on Glitterworlds for the beautiful changes to the body, such as the floral-like mutations that sprout around the ears. It is infamous on Urbworlds for the lethal toxins that some of the mutations secrete.

Ursa:
Forming beast like mutations, Ursa is primarily designed for use by special divisions of military shock troopers.

Igni:
Designed and mass produced to enhance manual labor, it promptly received a ban on various worlds when unintended mutations started popping up.

Myrol:
Myrol was produced for a specific mutation; Myrolsis, which bestows light regeneration and stronger blood filtration. However, most of its side effects are less than desirable.

Midia:
One of the earliest mind altering mutagens that was proven to be safe enough for specialized use.
</description>
</ModMetaData>